<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Delegate Uprising: The Best Way to Stop a Bullet is to Tell a Story]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Delegate Uprising: The Best Way to Stop a Bullet is to Tell a Story]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/delegate-uprising/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2016 21:56:35 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/delegate-uprising/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/645ec720-85f5-48ac-b87d-27b2e14061aa.jpg" alt="" title="">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/delegate-uprising/97b4ed23-a999-4e5c-ad91-5784840821e8/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">97b4ed23-a999-4e5c-ad91-5784840821e8</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2016 21:56:25 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Maryam]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Maryam</h1><p>My name is Maryam Ali. I am 17. I am Chinese. I am Pakistani. I am American. I am Muslim. I am a Woman. And my voice is being held captive against my will by restraints made of western bigotry. In every direction I turn I find people undermining my power, my voice, my intellect, my humanity, and my integrity. I grew up raised in a strict Islamic household, but I am not oppressed. I am not ISIS. And I should not and will not feel responsible or apologize for the crimes they have committed in the name of my peaceful religion.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/597249b1d0fe25f2d4968c747cd6e8e5b272f41a.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/delegate-uprising/maryam/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a61008d1-c802-472d-9a60-c9e4071825da</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2016 21:55:47 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lorax]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Lorax</h1><p>At what moment did you find what you wanted to do with the rest of your life? The moment I knew I wanted to pursue rapping did not come from a music video, nor did it come from the loud pulsating bass or a roaring crowd. It came from my 7th grade social studies class, watching a movie titled “Green”. A movie with no words, it vividly detailed the mass destruction of precious Indonesian rainforest for Palm Oil plantations, and chronicled the rescue and rehabilitation of an Orangutan in which the movie is named after. I loathed and decried the lack of empathy and evil that lied in humans, and it haunted me for a solid 3 years. Then, on a campaign trip in Youth and Government, I travelled down to LA. However instead of doing a speech, I rapped about the Orangutans, how we were destroying their home, and how we needed to burn the corporations to the ground. I was free from my pain. For the last year, I have been performing and debating with my friends in Youth and Government, made up of 3,000 California high schoolers, forming the Orangutan Posse. But last year, I had another gut punching experience, similar to the one in 7th grade. Except this time, it’s personal. On May 19th an Oil Pipeline burst open and spilled 105,000 gallons into our beloved Gaviota coast and beyond, poisoning animals, the ecosystem, and us. Just recently, the Oil is being investigated to have already traveled as far down as L.A. Oil is toxic, how are we going to clean it up? Plains All American Pipeline considers it an “inconvenience”. Tell that to the fisherman. The thousands of locals who’s hearts you turned black. Tell that to every Dolphin that suffocated on the devil’s juice you call Oil. Perhaps the most tragic thing is we have learned nothing since 1969 or BP in 2010, we have only made things worse. This time, you would think this would serve as a warning to both the state and federal government to switch to growing alternative energy sources. Instead, we saw our federal government supporting the conquests of Shell and Transcanada, the media shut down all coverage of the spill. I refuse to be silent and bought like our politicians. Walking the line of being a maniac and a hero is difficult, but someone has to do it. In November running for a position in Youth and Government, I decided I would just rap about controversial issues for a speech instead of speak because why not. Fast forward two months later, when I have build a network of thousands of friends who support me, when they called my name to rap I heard the loudest cheer I have ever been in a room with. Ever. I was able to speak my mind on the fact there are underdogs in society. The people animals and nature that is swept under. That no one cares about. I do not live for fame, but rather to have enough of an influence that I can reach a few underdogs in the audience to speak up for their independent empathetic thoughts, no matter what authority says, or what the system thinks is right. I am Lorax.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/a0914c24b9e4997c074625207d225784224eb5fa.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/delegate-uprising/lorax/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">e6932bd5-7293-4db0-9d3a-599a5e62c722</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2016 21:54:14 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Jake]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Jake</h1><p>Hi, My name is Jake Montes Adams. Most people understand to some extent that the history of the indigenous peoples of this country is a dark, sad one. But to a lot of people, that history is just history- a chapter in a textbook to be discussed in APUSH classrooms. When people talk about Native Americans, it’s usually in the past tense. In the minds of many we are gone, relegated to the same cultural space as the wild west and gold rushes. Our absence is known as an unfortunate side effect of the creation of a free, democratic nation.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/61ac7675c0f8599a63399eac97cc3d0d186bdfdc.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/delegate-uprising/jake/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">e84a40d2-7dd8-4127-b9da-2a36d434af4e</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2016 21:54:29 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Brendan]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Brendan</h1><p>Hey Youth and Government. I’m Brendan Thompson, a junior from the North Valley YMCA. Y & G has brought so much joy and passion into my life. Sacramento 2015 was probably the best week of my life. Unfortunately that’s not what I’ll be sharing with you today. What I will be sharing are my worst weeks, my lowest points and how I both overcame and learned from them.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/804b27d646b3897d5870955c6bfe1adfd687fd6b.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/delegate-uprising/brendan/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">563e1808-eb87-4d66-8caa-7c9651bcac5d</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2016 21:51:58 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>